Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Thank you for watching.
Well, uh, good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Are you here?
It's the fourth day of the Stardust Gamers Club.
Summer vacation special, Wednesday Night of Fear, Night 1.
I'm Hinata Kashiwagi.
I'm already scared.
I'm scared.
My hair's really trembling.
I'm afraid of you all.
Please don't comment or say anything that might scare me.
Please don't say things that might scare me.
I'm scared because I'm a coward.
I think everyone who's watching already knows I'm not good at this.
I've watched you for a long time.
The sound of a balloon popping makes me collapse.
And the mere sound of someone behind me scares me.
I can't even go to a haunted house.
Even if I did, I'd be screaming the whole time
I'd be moving around with my face in Mayama's butt
I really can't walk
I mean, really, really
Um, I'm scared, so I'm tryingUm, I'm scared, so I'm trying my best.
I've never played a horror game before.
I've never played before.
I'm too timid to play them.
I usually play something fun.
Like Momotetsu.
Mario.
Switch Sports, that kind of thing.
You know, while having fun.
I've been trying to have some kind of competition.
You know what I mean? The screen of this distribution...
There were lines and shiny things.
I thought it was a weird phenomenon.
Wasn't it bizarre? Something like that.
What is it? I heard it was something like that.
Right?
Yes, sir.
They say the sound is scary, right?
And maybe my voice is too quiet, right?
Maybe that's because I'm going to make more noise.
But I'm really scared.
But I really want to go home.
I need someone to do it.
Just for a minute.
What kind of horror game are we playing today?
It's called "Night Security.
What do you mean?
They said something about just guarding at night.
But that's definitely not what they said.
I'm pretty sure they're lying.
What's up? What's going on?
What's wrong? He says I'm... he can't hear me.
What do I do?
Can you hear me?
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
She says it's too quiet for you.She said it's too quiet for Hina-chan.
How's it sounding? She can hear me. She can hear you.
Well, I'll just keep going, since I'm in the middle of something and my big, fat voice might come out.
Maybe... maybe she's avoiding me.
Let's just...
What?
I can hear you, but it's low.
Maybe if I turn up the mike a little bit?
Is that possible?
I can hear you, but they're saying the volume's pretty low.
Wait a minute.
If this is regression, we're in trouble.
It's always low on game feeds. It's fine.
Okay, well, let's just keep going.
Okay, that's all right, go ahead.
I can tell my hands are in real trouble because they're shaking a little bit.
I don't know where it's going to come from, so I'll just hold the controller for now and get on with it.
Let's start from the beginning.
Okay...
Oh, my God!
Susu, it's moving.
What? With this.
Check it out.
What? What? You want me to go over here more?
What?
There's nothing here.
Oh, my God. There's nothing.
It's shaking. Hey.
Hey, it's not coming back. It's coming back.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
You're gonna check this one, too?
Let me check it out. Hey, what?
Hey, what?
Did you eat it? You didn't eat this?
I don't know. What do you want me to do?I don't know. What do I do?
I don't know what to do.
Oh, that's it.
There you go.
What am I supposed to do with this?
What do you want me to look up anyway?
You mean the game where you have to look up stuff for the rest of your life?
Yeah.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
This... this... picture... picture...
It's like this...
Ugh.
The kid drew this picture, right, Mr. Family?
I don't know what to do with it.
What do you want me to do? I don't know if there's anything left to say.
No, no, no. Yes, yes, yes.
He's not here.
What should I do with this?
Hey, what should we do? - Can you open this?
Yes...
It's a toilet. - Open all of them.
Open all of them!
Yes!
Yes, yes, yes.
Clean. - Laundry. Laundry, check this out.
I'm checking the laundry.
Don't jump out at me. No.
What? It's not here.
What's this? What's this?
Oh, shit, here it is.
What? Did I open it?
No, I didn't!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No!
It's open.
Hey, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.Hey, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
No!
Go away! Go away!
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
What is it?
Nothing. Nothing.
People.
Hey. Hey.
What's up? Just sleeping?
Just sleeping?
What do you want me to do?
Where are you going?
Where do you want me to go?
Should I open it? Ready!
Yee!
What, kids?
A child?
Is it a kid?
Come on.
Come on!
What?
What? You want to go to bed? Go to sleep. Good night!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Is this your mother? Where's Mom?
Mother? Mother?
Mom?
Mom, where are you?
Mother, it's yours.
Where's your father?
Oh, not quite like that.
I waited for you.I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Oh, what, hey.
This, this, this, this.
This, this, this.
What do I do with this?
What do I do with this? What do we do with it?
What do we do with it?
What?
Anybody?
From here.
We're getting out?
Out.
Uh...
It won't open.
What? You're gonna open it?
It opens.
What?
Congratulations.
What do we do now?
It's over.
I'll be 30 on October 29th.
Where is this coming from?
what are you doing?
oh, well, well, well
Well, well, well.
Flowers?
Hey.
Sadness the next day.
Eh, here we go.
You're down.
Where are you coming from? This. Is it going in the building?Where are you coming from? Where is it coming from? Is it going in the building?
This one? Oh, this is it.
Hey, I saw someone.
There he is again.
Hey.
That sounds good.
There was definitely someone here.
Hey. Hey.
What's up?
Right hand?
Is that...
Yeah.
Twelve o'clock.
What is it? What do you want me to do?
What are you looking up?
What is this?
It's a room...
Oh, no.
Room...
Why is there...
There's some kind of nice music playing.
I can't do this.
I'm gonna have to check one side of the house, turn off the key to the bathroom, and send you back to where the people are.
What is this?
What's with all the bad music?
What if it's the building security?
Calm down, Mr. Goto. I couldn't reach him.
He's probably down.
That's why I asked for you.
I heard this company has a rule against working overtime after midnight.
Clocks and monitors.
I want you to go over the security details.
I want you to make the rounds.
Thank you.
Yes, sir.
This one or this one from earlier. Fire extinguisher... toilet man.This one or this one from earlier. Fire-abandoned machine toilet person.
"Fire-abandoning toilet person. Fire-abandoning toilet person. Fire-abandoning toilet person.
I'm here.
Wait a minute.
I was a little too loud.
There's only one fire-engine toilet, right?
There you are.
Is this it?
What?
Hey.
Can I come in?
Scary! It's disgusting!
It's so dark!
What? Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
Hey!
I'm sweating so hard.
I'm not doing anything.
Is that...?
Is that a person?
No, it's not!
Hey!
I'm gonna cry now.
I'm scared!
Are you there? Hey, what if they're not there already? Hey!
Hey, why did you close the door? Who's there?
Hey, I didn't close it.
It's like they're going room by room.
Fire extinguisher? This? It's a fire alarm.
Mm-hmm.
What is it? What the hell?
Is he gone? Is it gone? Is he gone?
What if it's not there? Come on.
Is this place gonna open?
Open this door!Open it!
It's open!
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
Who's there?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Get out of here.
Ugh, it's so close!
Oh, my God, it goes right through here.
Hey, are you home?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone, I'm gone.
I'm not here. I'm leaving.
I want to go home. I want to go home.
There's still room.
I'm leaving.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, what is this place?
It's a bathroom.
Toilet!
Toilet.
Hmm?
What...
What are you... a man... Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
But are there any boys here?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
Bye.
Here it is.
It's open.
Hello? It's a chair.
Hey.
You didn't see anyone?
No?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Let's run.
Run! A little more.Run! A little more.
I don't know if this is okay. The first floor's empty.
There's nothing on the first floor. Wow, it closed on its own.
You know what?
You didn't turn off all the lights.
You turn off all the lights? The lights.
How?
They're not on here, are they? This one.
This one's not on, is it?
Let's say it's not working.
And then we'll go home, right?
Where's the light in the bathroom?
Where are the lights in the bathroom?
This one?
This?
Hey, did you know there was a fire escape? Hey, where are the lights in the bathroom? Isn't there any? Isn't this automatic? This or a fire-extinguisher. No? No, not this one.
I can't go any further.
There's a fire-extinguisher in the room. Oh, what's that? That glowing thing?
What?
What? This one? Oh, this.
What? What? All clear.
Okay, okay. Let's go home. Let's go home.
Oh, I didn't do all this. That sucks.
Mwah.
This one, too? Where is it?
I didn't do anything. I didn't even lock the door.
How do you lock the door?
I guess that means the lights aren't on.
You're sweating like a pig. I'm really scared.
What? Why did it close on its own?
Get out.
Shush.
Wrong way.
I don't know what to do.
What do you mean, "Okay"? What do you mean?What do you mean, "Okay"? Okay?
Where's "yes"?
Oh, there it is. There's the X.
Long press.
There you go. Okay.
It's closed.
Oh, is this for the bathroom, too?
Toilet's okay.
But there's no fire extinguisher, right?
Hey, I don't know what to do.
What do you want me to do?
What is it? It's ringing somewhere.
You said you'd turn off the lights in the bathroom.
I know, right?
Hey, I don't know where this is going.
Where's... what?
Hey.
Which one's the light? This one?
This one?
Oh, this isn't it.
Oh, it's this one.
What?
Ugh, it was on the inside. You definitely bumped it.
Oh, and this one?
This one's fine.
Huh.
Oh, what?
What?
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
This is taking forever.
This is where the person was, right?
All clear.
Let's get out of here.
Let's get out...
Locked.
Here we go.Here we go.
What's over here?
First floor for now.
Hey, did I do that?
Did I open this?
I don't know anymore.
I didn't do all this.
You're not doing any work.
Hey, hey, what's your job?
Something's coming!
Something's coming up. Be on the lookout.
It's closed.
Oh, shit.
This one too?
Is this one okay?
Here.
Ugh.
Oh, my God.
You did it already? This one.
You didn't? I don't even know if we did.
I don't even know which squads they're in and which ones they're not.
You know what?
I'm scared.
Hey.
We did it.
It's all clear, but it's not all clear.
You don't have to press a button.
Something about the game... we won again.
Hey, Doc.
Close the door.
Hey.
What's this?
Close.
I made it.
What are we gonna do with this?What are you going to do with this?
Oh, we already did this.
And this one?
This one's fine.
This one's good, too.
Oh, here, here, here, here, here, here.
Are we going upstairs?
Upstairs?
Oh, they said the first floor's clear.
Oh, shit.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
I'm looking at about 600 people.
Is this really what you want?
There's nothing here.
Upstairs?
I want to buy some tea.
Or coffee.
What's this?
Where are you going?
Oh, I'm scared.
There's nothing here.
What do we do now? We'll take a right.
Go right, then right again. This way.
This way again.
Oh, my God!
There's a man!
Good evening... this...
What's this? Are you, like, a...
You're so cool. Thank you.
What? Suddenly?
Why did you exchange contacts?
Wow, I hate women like this.
I won't leave without your number.
I won't make you regret it.
Oh!
You just walked right into my face, you know that?You just went right through my face, honey.
Where is it? There it is. There it is.
I mean, the lights are on in here.
Clear.
Where's the power?
Is there no electricity?
Oh, this is not electricity, this is my light.
Yes, ho degrees.
What's that? That's the same place as before.
Do we have to go in here?
Is it connected? If it's connected.
Let me close this for a second.
I've got the key.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to lock this one.
Where is it?
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared!
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
It's locked. And here it is.
I didn't know you were up.
The light's on.
What the hell?
Why do I see this ping-pong, ping-pong, ping-pong...
What's with the TV?
Oh, you have one of these? What is it?
What? !
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Next preview.
What? Someone's coming in.
I don't like it.
He's talking.
Who is it?
What did you do?
What is this?
What was that?What was it?
I don't know.
Well, good luck.
That's so impersonal.
Come on, help me out.
Hey, you know what?
Where's the power?
There's no power.
Oh, shit, it came out this way.
Oh, just close it.
There's no light.
It's not closed this way. It's not closed this way.
Is that electricity? Electricity? Electricity?
It's the toilet again.
Knock-knock.
He's not here.
What?
Who's there?
He said not to turn off the lights. Can't you turn off the lights? What if I do?
Will they get mad if I turn it off? You can't turn off the light?
I couldn't.
Well, goodbye.
I'm going to go out the door for a minute.
I'm scared, I really am.
What? A woman? A woman?
That's the sound of the second floor closing.
I'm going to...
Okay, I'm going to the third floor.
You want me to go to the third floor?
I'm the only one on the third floor.
What? It's close, it's close.
I want to push it to the third floor.
Here, hold on a sec. Let me get a glass of water.
It won't open. Oh, my God.
I can't get the bottle open. My hand.I can't open the bottle. My hand.
Wait, the bottle won't open. My hand.
My hand.
Are you on it? It won't open.
Thank you very much.
Are you on it?
It's not open.
I didn't push it.
Did you push it?
It's not open.
Oh, God. Oh, God, it's a galleon.
It's been 11 times, maybe 10, I don't know.
Someone's in there.
That's very, very close.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Anybody?
No?
I tried to run away from here.
It's gone!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What? What the hell?
Why don't you just tighten it?
You're good.
Road.
Hey, I already know someone's here.
Thank you for watching.
Okay, let's get started.
I'm scared!
I'm not doing this by tomorrow.
What's that look in your eyes?
What the hell?
What's with the big ice cream?What the hell is a major ice cream company?
what the hell is a rosenbrock ice cream?
What the hell is a roasted block of ice cream?
This is the most beautiful thing you've ever made.
Hey, you listening to me?
What? Why?
We're on the third floor, okay?
Hey, we're on the third floor!
I'm on the third floor. Why are you here?
It's the same guy.
You're scaring me!
Hey.
I can't check.
What is it? Is it coming out?
What is it? It's not there?
What?
I don't know.
I don't know. I'm turning it off.
Why don't you just turn off the light?
Did you turn off this light?
Did you turn it off?
What? What's wrong?
I'm scared.
Why are you scared? Earlier, I was...
Am I on the second floor at all?
Upstairs?
Third floor!
What?
I spent it on the third floor!
He used it on the third floor.
And this is it.
This is the room we just left.That's the room we just left.
There's the inspector.
He's out.
What do you want me to do?
Oh, God.
What's going on? What's going on?
It's scary!
What?
What was that?
Did you see that?
It's another lorry.
Oh, oh, shit.
It's sideways, isn't it?
What? Why do people come here?
Oh.
What do you want me to do for you?
I just want it to stop.
I can't do anything.
Earthquake doorbell.
Don't cry.
What's here?
There's nothing here.
Oh, it's such a small place
Oh, I'm going to search in a small area like this
Oh, it's not here.
It's gone.
They're not here.
Eighty-eight!
Money money money money money money
Hmm...
You're a real wander
Wander.
Why?
Do you do electricity right?
Oh, did you see this?Oh, have you seen this place?
Let's close it.
Dazu, what do you remember?
Veteran.
Missing speak
Stress
Tired
There was a person.
People.
I'm scared.
Don't come out of nowhere.
I was so scared. I had my fingers in the air.
They told me I had to finish this job by morning.
There was no way I could finish.
It's like Mr. Hamaura... but it's my body again.
I was so scared, I thought it was a severed head.
There's nothing here.
I didn't even close the door.
He's here.
Hey...
Cat, it's making noise!
Oh, no.
What are we gonna do with this?
Oh, I know, I know. Toilet. Toilet.
Nice toilet. Nice toilet.
I thought I was gonna have to replace it.
Where is it?
I'm scared.
What was that? Whose voice?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Who's saying that?
Is it me?
Hey!Hey!
I'm here, I'm here, I'm here.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
Aaargh!
He's not here.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I can't get it in, I can't get it in, I can't get it in.
Hmm?
Hey, is he in there?
No, I don't see him.
He's not here.
Hey.
What?
He's not here?
Oh, my God.
I was just on my way.
He's not here.
Oh, my God.
What do I do?
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I just saw it.
I'm going home.
There it is.
Oh, I want to change it. What do you want me to do?
I want to change this.
Oh, hey, I want to change the fluorescents.
I can't change it.
Oh, I don't know how to do this.
I can't get it to do anything.
What do I do?
What do I do with this? Somebody...
What do I do with this?
What, the gift shop?
Oh, that?
Hey, guys, can you help me out? That's so sweet of you.Hey guys can you help me out? Thank you so much for your kindness.
Thank you so much.
Where's the Beauty Parlor?
Right here.
Oh, this is it.
This?
What? This one?
Which one?
This one?
You can't touch it.
What? I'm supposed to go closer?
Oh, that's it. I'm supposed to go closer.
I got it. Frog, frog, frog, frog.
Oh, well, I can't.
Yes, yes, yes.
That was fun. That was fun. That was really fun.
Fun. Fluorescent light.
I changed it. I'm done.
I said I cleared it four times.
It's still there.
What's that sound?
Booth.
There it is again.
What's wrong with you? It's dark.
It's dark.
Where's the electrical room?
Hey, where's the... where's the... where's the...
What do I do? What do I do?
I don't know what to do.
Hey. Oh, here.
There's a fuse missing. A fuse.
Hey, hey, what's a fuse? Fuse.
What's a fuse? What's a fuse?
It's dark. It's dark.
What? What? What? What? Oh, it's not a person.
Hey, I'm tired.Hey, I'm tired.
Your voice.
What's that? Is that it?
What's this?
Hey, hey, there's a missing fuse. What's a fuse?
Hey, it's very scary. It's dark.
I don't like it.
Hey, hey, I want to turn on the lights.
What's a fuse?
I don't know where to go.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna have to turn on all these lights and look around.
What's a fuse?
There's something red over there.
There's something over here!
Hey, scary!
Here...
What? It's so dark!
Hey!
What? It's a wall!
It's all walls.
What?
What's this? Where are you going?
It's a wall.
What? What is it?
What is this?
I can't touch it.
I don't know where to go.
I'm about to cry.
Yes?
What is it?
Hey, hey, hey.
What's this room?
Hey, what's this?
What's this? We're in the wrong place, aren't we? There's no classroom.You're in the wrong place, aren't you? There's no classrooms.
What is this? What are we gonna do?
It's a maze!
What? It's a maze!
I don't know what to do.
It's like I'm stuck in a maze.
That's where we were. We're back.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, what do we do with this? Is this it?
I just got a fuse, an electrical one, but something weird happened.
Hey, somebody.
What? Huh? What? It's a gram can.
But I can't push it on anything.
Hey, what do I do with this?
Hey, what do you want me to do?
What do we do? They say I'm lost, but I'm not. I'm totally lost.
What is this? What is this? What is this? I want to go home, but I don't know what to do.
I don't know...
I'm totally lost. What do I do?
Did you get it? Did you see this?
Where's this?
Hey, we already passed it.
What are you doing with this?
Which way are we going?
What's this?
What? Don't you want to go through there?
Hey, I can't get out.
Hey, hey, hey, what are we supposed to do?
If you keep alternating, you'll never get out. I'm pretty sure that's right. You have to go further in.
We have to go to the back. I don't even know where the back is.
I don't even know where the back is.
Hey, I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
What is it?
Hey, I found it.
Hey, Hewes, when you said you found it in your hand...
How do we get home?
You don't know how to get home?Don't you know how to get home?
Hey, hey, hey, I don't know how to get home.
Can I go now?
I don't know.
Can we just go? Some place?
Where am I going? How far is this?
We just passed it.
Where is it?
This way, this way.
Oh, my God.
What the...
What? The ocean is so much easier.
It's all...
Wow! That hurt, it hurt, it hurt!
Itchy, itchy, itchy!
People!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...
...
I'm gonna cry... cry...
Oh, I'm scared...
Oh, my God...
Hey, what should I do?
I'm already crying.
I'm scared
What should I do?
Hey...
Do...
Here.
What do we do?
Hey. Hey.
Hey. Hey.Hey.
Oh, my God.
Ew.
Where is it?
Where is this?
Where's...
Oh, my God! Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Where is it?
I don't know.
It's like... it's like... it's like... it's like... it's like...
Oh, here.
This is it.
I think the lights came on.
Oh, my God!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is it.
After this, he was going home by By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By By
By going home to his home by going home to his home by going home to his home
No one has arrived he
Endure
Take off his clothes
For the first time
I'm digging in.
And the world
Thank you for watching.
What are your goals for the future?
Please tell us about any goals you have for future activities.
[QUESTION] What are your goals when promoting your future activities?
Thank you for watching.
Is the sound back on this?
Is the audio back?
I'm sorry. I'm scared already.
You scared me.I got spooked.
I broke the microphone.
I'm scared. I'm scared all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared... I'm scared...
I don't know what to do
Who was that? Who was it?
I'm sorry, I'm scared.
What are you doing here?
What?
Hey, lift four levers.
What levers?
I don't know. The ones you just lifted.
Hey, lift four more levers.
Diagnostics.
I'm having a hard time.
Oh, this one.
Good boy.
Oh!
Yeah.
hmm?
Oh, here it is.
Which one's left?
There's more.
This one?
Hey, who's here?
Wrong lever.
I'm scared.
I don't know what to do.
One more.
I'm scared.
I'm scared
I'm scaredI'm scared.
Is that it?
Is that the one I gave you?
That's the one I gave you.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, this way.
This way.
It looks like it's this way.
Here?
No, no, no.
Where is it?
It's not here.
There's no lever.
A lever?
This one?
You just did that, too. There's no lever.
There's no lever. There's no lever.
Is the lever gone? Is it done?
Turn on the light. Where's the lever?
Where's the lever? I wonder if there's another one back there.
Oh, no.
He's not here.
Hey, there's no lever.
Lever.
Heh.
There's no lever.
There's no lever anywhere.
Lever.
I don't know what to do. There's no lever.
Hey, there's no lever!
Oh, here it is... here it is... here it is.
It's that crafted type.That crafting ceremony.
I wrote something about watching it in the surveillance room.
Let's just lock up for now.
Let's just lock the door.
I'm scared.
There's so much going on.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
How do we even see it? You mean like on the first floor?
The first floor, the second floor. Oh, that's scary.
What floor am I on? Oh, my God.
What is this?
What's with that guy?
What are you looting?
Don't pillage.
Don't sleep with him.
What's this?
What is this conversation?
What the fuck?
What the hell?
He's running from the tree!
What the hell, women are attracted to little devils.
Check the surveillance camera on the other side for more.
Blood!
What's this?
What?
Who's this?
Who's there? Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
I don't know what to do with this.
What?
What is this?
What do I do?
What? What do I do?What? What?
What am I supposed to do with this?
Do I go back?
Do we go back?
Fourth floor?
How do we go back?
You can go back.
I'm back.
Oh, my God.
Good night, sweetheart.
Good night. - Good night.
I'm so lucky.
You guys have made it possible for me to endure.
And you're taking all the blame.
But what if he quits?
Oh, no!
I'd probably hate him if he did.
That's true.
You're right.
What's this?
What is this?
This is so creepy.
Oh, my God.
Is this okay?
Can we get out of here?
Mm-hmm.
You don't have to lock this door.
I closed this one... with the key and the lock.
I'm scared.
I don't know if I can go to the bathroom yet.
I'm already scared.
Hey.
Hey! What's this?
What is this?
What is this?what is this?
I'm scared.
Is this it?
Is there something in here?
What's this?
That was the door.
What is it? Clear?
People. People.
What is it? What is it?
What is it?
Hey, what's this?
Oh, my God.
Oh, it's cut off here.
Hey.
What floor are we on?
Fifth floor.
Mm-hmm.
Look, I can't do this all today.
I'm gonna stop next time.
I'm quitting. I'm quitting next time.
I'll quit next time.
I'm scared. It's so hard.
Oh, man...
I don't want to go
I don't want to go. I don't want to go.
I don't want to go anymore.
What do I do?
Come on, come on, come on.
What's this?
Oh, my God.
I'm scared.
Why is Moody's music playing here?
Hey, what are we gonna do with this?
What, you can't touch this guy?
Hey, lady?Hey, Auntie?
Is this your aunt?
Oh, you're the cleaning lady?
No!
What do you look like?
Where are you going? !
You're disgusting!
Hey, is she back there? I know you're in there. I know you're in there!
What am I supposed to do?
What? This place?
Why is it so rough? Hey.
Hey, this music is annoying.
What am I supposed to do with this?
I can't.
Oh, yeah, there's four 3s.
Hm.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
what do i do?
Oh, my God.
I'm scared. I don't like it.
Oh, no, there's no one here.
Can I go home now?
I want to go home.
I'm scared.
Ha-ha-ha. Cleaning already.
I'm cleaning already.
No, no, no, no!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Mike, I'm sorry!
I'm closing.
I saw it!
I just saw it!
Oh, this way.
I didn't check it already.
What's that?Huh?
Huh...
Oh, God, I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die.
Oh, my God! What?
Look at this. Lilly.
Did you see it? You saw it, right?
You saw it, right?
Oh, my God!
Oh, a chair.
I thought it was a person.
I saw it.
I saw this.
Oh, my God.
Huh.
What! Auntie!
She's looking at me!
Oh, no!
Move!
Hey!
My aunt...
Hey. Hey.
What do I do?
She's looking at me.
Why aren't you saying anything?
I'm leaving. I'm leaving.
Just a little bit more. I really can't today.
Let's just get this over with.
Can we just get in?
If I get in, is it over?
Uh...
What, do I just close it? The door.
Like this?As is?
What? It closed on its own.
We're all done, today.
Oh, I cried.
I'm scared.
I mean, I didn't even get through it.
How many times do I have to do this?
Eleven?
You've done it six times now?
Seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven?
And we're going to go this far?
I can't do this.
That's what I'm saying.
I heard there's a sequel.
We'll be back on Wednesday, the 16th of August at 8:30 p.m.
This is so bad.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Well...
What are we going to do?
It's so different.
This is the first horror game I've ever seen people do this in.
No.
No one.
Well, it's been a while since I've played a game like this.
I don't know.
It's not that I'm disappointed that I lost.
I don't know what to say.
I don't feel anything. I'm just scared.
My eyes are all shiny.
I didn't think I'd make such a fuss.
I mean, all of a sudden... you're right behind me... and I'm like, "Who?
Who's done this before?
Have any of you ever done this night guard thing?
I have.
I think I've seen it.I'm sure you've seen it before.
I mean, how do you guys feel when you watch me play games?
It's not about fun, it's about hearts.
It's a heart. The staff said it was a heart.
It's so scary.
Oh, my God.
I'm really a reactionary comedian.
Anyway, I'll see you in a week, Wednesday the 16th of August at 8:30 p.m.
I'm going to continue with this at 8:30 p.m., and I'm going to do my best to get through it.
I'm going to do it five times, five times, because, you know, it's going to be even scarier than before.
I can't do it anymore. Hey, I'm really sorry I broke your microphone.
I'm sorry.
Thank you very much.
You've got a lot of great conversations, don't you?
Like, "I'm popular because I'm a devil.
"I'm more attractive than he is.
Like, "Let's exchange contact information.
Like, "If you don't exchange contacts, I can't leave.
She's quite a woman, isn't she?
That's amazing.
Hey, hey, hey.
Let's just... let's just...
I'll keep working on it, I promise.
I'll do my best.
I'm really sorry, what was that?
The Hoodie song.
That's the funniest part.
It starts so abruptly.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, I guess that's it for today.
It's been a little over an hour.
Good job.
I'm on night duty.
I don't know.
I didn't even look it up.I didn't even look it up.
I thought it would be more fun to do it for the first time.
That's why I thought it would be more interesting if I did it for the first time.
I'm sure I'll tell you about it, but...
I should have looked it up.
But I'm pretty sure Midoi forgot too, so here's what happened.
This is what happens when you do it for the first time.
I wanted to do something like this.
I'd love to do it.
Thank you for watching.
If I say "head" here, it's not good, right?
Well, we're going to continue with this for now, so...
How many people watched today?
Six people saw it... 600...
Oh, what? They're gone.
Oh, I'm scared.
What?
Oh, I'm sorry. What?
What do you want me to do?
Have them take the footage.
I'm sorry, this is, this is what I'm talking about,
Thank you for watching.
Thank you for watching